Geez.
-This place is a mess.
-Mm.
You ever hear of a trash can?
-And I know you know
how to fold.
Uh-uh. Get up.
You know good and well I did not
raise a son this lazy.
Get on up now.
It's close to noon.
Yeah?
:
Hey, it's Earn.
Um, just checking in.
You
Al?
Yeah, man. I'm-I'm-I'm...
yeah, I'm okay.
All right. Good.
Um, did you get a chance
to look over those forms yet?
They need them to be signed
by Wednesday.
Nope. I, um...
I ain't get a chance yet.
-Okay. Just...
-Yeah.
* Eat, sleep *
* Everybody wanna be a nigga,
but nobody wanna be a nigga *
* When it's time to be a nigga *
* Please, 'cause if I get
nervous we get un-sturdy *
* And we start to squeeze,
okay, niggadom. *
What's up, bro?
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah.
Hungry?
Nah, bruh. I'm good.
You sure? I just learned
how to make pasta.
Nigga, when'd you learn
to make pasta?
In a dream.
Yeah, Mayor McCheese was there,
the girl from Dharma and Greg...
-Oh, that's, um...
that's my ride, man.
I'll see you later.
Is that Sierra?
Yeah.
-Mm.
What, man?
Nothing, man. I just, you know,
I thought you were allergic
to girlfriends.
-Man, Sierra ain't
my girlfriend.
-Okay.
Well, make sure you ask her
if she wants some
of this fire pasta. Yeah?
I will, um,
keep that in mind, bruh.
-I'll see you later.
-Mm-hmm.
All right, I'm serious, man.
I'm-a put my foot up in this.
(car engine revs,
hip
* I need some drop,
I need some drop *
-* I need a bird *
-* Brr, brr *
* Color like Durk... *
ALFRED:
What's up, girl?
* 4:00 a.m.
I'm just gettin' started *
* For my birthday,
I threw me a surprise party *
* Reminiscin' 'bout the trap *
* Playin' the first Carter *
* My life changed when I had
my first daughter *
* Got my first quarter
flippin' $50 slabs *
* Your nigga lookin'
at the bills... *
You know I used to dance
around here, right?
In that strip club right there.
* So you kind of the boss *
* You keep playin' with me... *
Yeah. Yeah, you told me.
You ever go in there?
Shit. Sometimes.
Well, maybe you seen me
there before.
Like, before we was
anything special.
Shit, I could've been grinding
on your junk
thinking you was just another
dumb, broke nigga.
-Mm-hmm.
And I could've thought you was
just another stuck-up ho
with too many damn
stretch marks.
* Drop a pin,
send a location... *
You crazy, girl.
God, I'm so glad
you could kick it today.
-Yeah.
I swear,
I don't see nobody no more.
It's just photo shoots
and appearances.
Shit is crazy.
Yeah, I hear that.
Yeah. You get it, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm.
It's nice to be around someone
who gets it.
DJ :
106.5 The Jam.
Nothing but the hits.
* Uh, uh... *
Oh, shit.
Aah!
Yeah!
* Hey, yeah, Paper... *
How's it going?
Go over here?
SIERRA:
Yo, Alfred.
Yo.
SIERRA:
You should get these shoes.
ALFRED:
I ain't got no interest
in looking like no damn
black Aladdin.
SIERRA:
Ugh. Whatever.
That "dope boy from the hood"
act won't last long.
Really? Since when
can you tell the future?
-Uh, since I'm about that money.
Y-You keep being smart,
but I'm serious.
People gonna get tired
of seeing a sweaty nigga
in a polo and cargo shorts.
Nobody wants somebody famous
to look just like them.
Yo, how much are they?
Man, who cares?
If you like them,
have your manager get them
for you for free.
Yeah, that ain't happening.
Yeah, why?
'Cause Earn, man, he don't...
he don't know
how to do all that.
He don't get you free shit?
I mean, he get me liquor
sent to the house sometimes,
-but other than that...
Oh, my God! Baby.
Baby, you got to level up.
Get you a manager
with a big dick.
You know, girl, I don't know
nothing about all that.
Look, enough
with the kiddie shit.
You need someone
who's working for you.
-Whatever, girl.
-Mm-hmm.
Uh, hello?
Can we get some assistance?
He needs to see a couple sizes
in this shoe.
-Yeah.
You bossing
white people around, huh?
Hey, somebody got to do it.
ALFRED:
I got you.
*
Aw.
Huh?
Ah, that girl
just posted that picture.
So sweet.
I love fans.
Huh. Ooh!
-I'm sorry.
It tickled. I-I-I'm sorry.
I ain't never felt nothing
like that before.
Oh, you know, most guys would
not be caught dead in here.
Is that right?
Hell yeah. Niggas be acting
like grooming theirself is gay.
That shit's fucked up.
-Ain't nothing wrong
with caring about your hair,
your nails, your skin.
Most niggas need makeup
more than I do.
You don't need makeup.
Aw, you're so sweet.
No, I'm serious.
It's my brand.
I'm Instagram famous, boo.
I can't be selling my wigs,
and out here looking janky.
I got to compete with
white girls with lip fillers
and butt injections, selling
lip gloss and spray tan.
Shit.
Everybody want
to be a black girl,
but the black girls ain't
making no money from it.
Hey!
Watch it.
Um, you need to post
on Instagram more.
No, no.
I hope your manager's
figured that out.
-He...
He's a...
It don't even matter.
Hey, look, no offense,
but, um...
I ain't into all that fake shit.
I'm just trying to stay real.
Oh, that's funny?
That shit funny to you?
Kinda.
Shit, you on the radio,
and you making money.
You been not real.
SIERRA:
Uh-uh. Uh-uh, uh-uh.
Y'all got to speak English
if you working on me.
Don't play with me.
I will call Marco over here,
and he will bounce
both of your asses out the door.
See? See, when they start
speaking in another language,
that's when you know
they talking shit.
Especially her.
She got a attitude
every time I come up in here,
talking to me up out her nose.
Man, why you bring me here?
Hmm?
We hanging, Paper Boi.
Sh...
Look. I just think
we could be good together.
Okay, so you want a boyfriend?
We can get that money.
We already getting money.
We can attach our brands.
Boost each other...
Look, we don't even
have to fuck all the time.
We just got to give them
something to talk about.
Something like... this.
Hey... Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Delete that picture, Sierra.
Why?
'Cause I told you, I ain't into
that weird-ass fake shit.
Uh, why are you so moody today?
Because you ain't ask
my permission to take that,
-that's why.
Nigga, you famous.
Look, just delete
the damn photo, Sierra!
What was I supposed to
say, "please"?
-I just told you,
-I ain't about that...
-What, nigga,
'cause you real?
:
Fuck this.
You sitting over there, whining,
acting like you better than me
'cause I'm trying to get paid.
Wake the fuck up.
That shit ain't real.
Look, I ain't got to stop
being me, all right?
That's something boring-ass
people like your ass got to do.
Well, where you going?
ALFRED:
I'm leaving.
I drove.
I can walk, ho.
*
TEEN: I told you, like,
50 times, man.
There are no zero gravity scenes
in Star Wars.
-Nigga, you ain't even seen
those movies.
Why the fuck do you care?
Whoa!
You Paper Boi.
What's up, man?
Yo, this is so crazy.
We've been listening to you
from the start.
Man, we love
that new song, bruh.
I've been driving
my momma crazy with it.
I appreciate that, man.
When I tell my brother
about this, he gonna trip.
-Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah. So what
are you doing here?
-I'm just living, man.
You ain't got no car?
(train whistle blowing
in distance)
I ain't allowed to walk?
Aw, you keeping it real.
That's what's up.
Yeah, that's right.
TEEN 2:
Yeah.
Well, shit.
-I got his watch!
Oh, shit!
TEEN:
Paper Boi!
-Hey, Paper Boi!
-Fuck!
Where the fuck
you think you're going?
Fuck!
Shit.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Who's that?!
MAN:
"Who's that?" That, that, that.
What the fuck, man?
"
-Shit.
Hey, look, man, I don't-I don't
want no trouble, all right?
I'm just passing through.
You looking for them boys?
Them bad boys?
Yeah. Yeah, you seen
which way they went?
Yeah, I seen.
Th-They went that way.
Then they went that way.
Then they went there.
-No.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm just high.
-Nah, man.
Come on. Let me
give you some money.
You can't go to the dance
without no money, boy.
Let old Wally help you out.
Wait. Wait!
Please!
I lost my baby.
What?
Take some ChapStick.
I don't like sharing lip to lip.
You got germs?
Don't follow me, man.
(insects trilling,
leaves fluttering)
Man, will you shut
the hell up, man?
Stop following me!
Take your ass home.
-You in bad shape, boy.
-Oh, shit.
Oh, come on, man.
That's you.
Deer guts.
That's what I'll call you.
Big ol' black-boy deer guts.
You're stubborn.
You're stubborn,
and you're black.
I'm serious, man.
Leave me the fuck alone!
Boy, you is just like your mama.
What?
What's the matter?
You looking all crazy.
Don't think you can out-slip me.
MAN:
Why you sitting?
I'm tired, man.
I'm tired.
I had a very bad day.
Shit.
Ah.
I-I just need to think, man.
Boy...
-ain't nobody could do that.
Nigga, you so damn useless.
You better watch how you
talk to people, deer guts.
You sit around in people's
houses insulting 'em.
You better stand up
and make a decision
about how you
getting out of here.
Nigga, just leave me alone.
Goddamn.
Make the decision.
Nigga...
Keep standing still,
you're gone, boy.
You're wasting time.
And the only people
who got time are dead.
And if you're dead,
I'm gonna take them shoes
and your wallet
and that shirt.
All right.
I...
Okay.
Just...
Shit.
MAN:
I'm-a count to 30,
and if you ain't walked out
of here by then,
I'm gonna hurt you,
'cause ain't nobody out here
but you and me, boy.
One... two... three...
12...
11... 13...
14... 15... 17...
Shit!
KID:
Hey, excuse me.
A
Uh, yeah, man.
Yeah, I'm Paper Boi.
You want a picture?
Come on.
All right. There you go.
-Yeah, yeah. I got it.
-All right.
Ready?
Got to give,
like, a mob face, man.
Yeah.
Do it again.
You got it?
Take another one.
Go ahead.
All right, man.
-Thank you.
-Yep.
Be safe out here.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH